Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, 1967-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1967-1993, I.; Item 1-149
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 184, 28 February 1981, 1 45 minute cassette; Container title: Paris in the 20s II Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 184)
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_184_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_184_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_184_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_184_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_184_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_184_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_184_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_184_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_184_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_184_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 185, 2 February 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Pioneers 1/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Program entitled: American pioneers No. 1 Capricorn; Studio recording Derivative files created: 19 (Box 4, Item 185)
    Contents: Ives: Set no. 1: The see'r; A lecture; The new river; Like a sick eagle; Calcium light night; Incantation (Allegretto sombreoso; Nancarrow: Chamber piece no. 1; Sidelights on American pioneers; Nancarrow: Trio; Ives: Set no. 2: The Indians; Gyp; The last reader; Nancarrow: Chamber piece no. 2? (or repeat of no.1); Ives: Four ragtime dances
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_185_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_185_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_01-15pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_185_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_185_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_01-15sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_185_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 186, 2 February 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Pioneers 2/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Program entitled American pioneers No. 1 Capricorn; Studio recording Derivative files created: 4 (Box 4, Item 186)
    Contents: Seeger: Quartet; Nancarrow: Studies nos. 2, 3b, 25, 3d -- Quartet; Seeger: Two movements for chamber orchestra
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_186_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_186_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_186_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_186_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_186_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_186_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_186_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_186_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_186_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_186_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 187, 2 February 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Pioneers 3/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Program entitled: American pioneers No. 1 Capricorn; Studio recording Derivative files created: 25 (Box 4, Item 187)
    Contents: Unidentified contents
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_187_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_187_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-15pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-16pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_01-17pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_187_02-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_187_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-15sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-16sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_01-17sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_187_02-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 188, 20 June 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Pioneers 4/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Program entitled: American pioneers No. 1 Capricorn; Broadcast Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 188)
    Contents: Prayers of steel
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_188_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_188_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_188_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_188_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_188_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_188_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_188_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_188_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_188_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_188_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_188_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_188_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 189, 1978, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Prokofiev Memoriam 1978 II Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location All 3 files for oboe and piano, possibly one work in 3 movements? Derivative files created: 3 (Box 4, Item 189)
    Contents: Piano works by Serge Prokofiev
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_189_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_189_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_189_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_189_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_189_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_189_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_189_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 190, 1978, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Prokofiev Memoriam 1978 I Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Spoken intro; Sarcasms, multiple works per file Derivative files created: 2 (Box 4, Item 190)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_190_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_190_01am.wav.norm.wav, ubmu0001_6_190_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_190_01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_190_02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_190_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_190_02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 191, 12 December 1975, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Ravel 12-12-75 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Suze Leal Rehfuss, mezzo-soprano; Stephen and Frida Manes, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby Contents from printed program need verification Derivative files created: 12 (Box 4, Item 191)
    Contents: Ravel: Sonata no.1 for violin and piano -- Chanson eccossaise -- Un grand sommeil noir -- Chanson de rouet -- Frontispiece -- Sites auriculaires -- La vallee des cloches -- Serenade grotesque -- Alborada del gracioso -- Si morne -- Ballade de la reine morte d'aimer -- Tripatos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_191_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_191_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_191_02-06pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_191_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_191_02-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 192, 12 December 1975, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Ravel - Gaspard de la nuit Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby Derivative files created: 1 (Box 4, Item 192)
    Contents: Ravel: Gaspard de la nuit
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_192_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_192_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_192_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 193, 11 December 1982, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Revivals + Premieres Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Katherine Cornell Theatre, University at Buffalo Program entitled: A piano recital of revivals and premieres; Honoring the 50th anniversary of the founding of the original Black Mountain College and John Cage's 70th birthday Derivative files created: 14 (Box 4, Item 193)
    Contents: Cowell: Advertisement -- Banshee; Ornstein: A la chinoise; Cage: In a landscape -- Suite for toy piano; Curran: For Cornelius; Wolff: Prelude no. 11; Cage: 49 waltzes for Black Mountain College II; Feldman: Intermission 5; Foss: Solo; Cage: Dream
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_193_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_193_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_193_02-07pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_193_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_193_02-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 194, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Rehearsal Mikhashoff + Nancarrow Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 194)
    Contents: Rehearsal of unidentified works by Conlon Nancarrow
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_194_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_194_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_194_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_194_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_194_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_194_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_194_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_194_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_194_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_194_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_194_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 195, 1 April 1979, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Ruders 4-1-79 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; University [at Buffalo] Philharmonia, James Kasprowicz, conductor Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby Derivative files created: 4 (Box 4, Item 195)
    Contents: Ruders: Recitatives and arias for piano and small orchestra
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_195_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_195_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_195_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_195_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_195_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_195_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_195_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_195_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_195_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_195_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 196, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Satie w/ Aki Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Aki Takahashi, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 21 (Box 4, Item 196)
    Contents: Satie: Trois morceaux en forme de poire -- Parade -- La belle excentrique (fantaisie serieuse -- Trois petites pièces mont é es -- Socrate
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_196_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_196_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-15pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-16pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-17pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_196_02-18pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_196_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-15sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-16sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-17sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_196_02-18sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 197, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Satie - Cage Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Aki Takahashi, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 6 (Box 4, Item 197)
    Contents: Satie: Nocturnes nos. 1-5 -- Rêverie de l'enfance de Pantagruel -- Premier menuet -- Relâche -- Cinema; Cage: Furniture music
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_197_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_197_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_197_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_197_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_197_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_197_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_197_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_197_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_197_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_197_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_197_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_197_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_197_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_197_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 198, 21 September 1986, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Satie by V.T. + Y.M. Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Virgil Thomson, narrator Recording location: Merkin Concert Hall (New York, N.Y.) Dolby B English translation by Virgil Thomson; recorded live by WNYC-FM; program entitled: Americans in Paris Derivative files created: 2 (Box 4, Item 198)
    Contents: Satie: Sports et divertissments
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_198_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_198_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_198_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_198_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_198_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_198_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 199, 21 September 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Satie - Thomson I Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Virgil Thomson, narrator Recording location: Studio and Merkin Concert Hall (New York, N.Y.) Dolby B English translation of Sports et divertissements by Virgil Thomson Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 199)
    Contents: Satie: Sports et divertissments (studio); Cage; Thomson: Portraits
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_199_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_199_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_199_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_199_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_199_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_199_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_199_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_199_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_199_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_199_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_199_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_199_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 200, 21 September 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Satie - Thomson II Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Virgil Thomson, narrator Recording location: Merkin Concert Hall (New York, N.Y.) Dolby B English translation pf Sports et divertissements by Virgil Thomson; recorded live by WNYC-FM; program entitled Americans in Paris Derivative files created: 4 (Box 4, Item 200)
    Contents: Thomson: Portraits (continued); Felder: Rocket summer; Satie: Sports et divertissments (live version)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_200_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_200_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_200_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_200_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_200_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_200_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_200_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_200_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_200_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_200_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 201, 20 October 1983, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Skandinavian + Carter Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby B Derivative files created: 6 (Box 5, Item 201)
    Contents: Ornstein: Afternoon in Chinatown -- Legend I; Olsen: Three nocturnes; Norgaard: Achilles and the tortoise; Carter: Night fantasies; Sellars: Concertorama toccata
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_201_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_201_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_201_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_201_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_201_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_201_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_201_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_201_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_201_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_201_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_201_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_201_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_201_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_201_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 202, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: James Sellars Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 202)
    Contents: Sellars: Toccata from Concertorama
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_202_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_202_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_202_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 203, 19 October 1980, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Sellars / Mikhashoff: Songs Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Joanne Scattergood, soprano Recording location: Real Art Ways (Hartford, Conn.) Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 203)
    Contents: Sellars: Songs; Mikhashoff: Songs
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_203_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_203_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_203_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_203_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_203_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 204, 4 July 1984, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Concertorama: James Sellars Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Outdoor concert, Hartford, Conn. very poor recording Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 204)
    Contents: Concertorama
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_204_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_204_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_204_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 205, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Sellars Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Dolby Probably only contains Sellars. Only recorded on Side 2? Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 205)
    Contents: Sellars: Piano concerto; Austin: Sonata concertante
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_205_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_205_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_205_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 206, 1986, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Sellars Performers: Jeffrey Krieger, cello; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Dolby B date of copyright is 1986 Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 206)
    Contents: Sellars: Separate ways
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_206_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_206_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_206_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 207, 15 May 1967, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Senior recital Performers: Ronald MacKay (Mikhashoff), piano Recording location: Department of Music, University of Houston Derivative files created: 8 (Box 5, Item 207)
    Contents: Bartók: Improvisations I-VIII; Chopin: Etudes op.25, nos. 12, 1, 2 -- Nocturne op.32, no.1 -- Etudes op.25, nos. 6, 8, 7 -- Prelude op.28, no.24; Debussy: Images pour piano: I. Cloches; II. Et la lune; III. Poissons d'or; Fennimore: Variations on a theme
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_207_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_207_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_207_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_207_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_207_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 208, 22 June 1977, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Shadows... Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello; William Kirkpatrick, dancer; Paul Schmidt, speaker Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Program entitled: Shadows, puppets, and clowns; date of 1987 on spine label is incorrect Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 208)
    Contents: Debussy: Cello sonata "Pierrot angry with the moon..." -- The toy box; Satie: Sports and diversions; Cage: Theatre piece
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_208_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_208_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_208_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_208_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_208_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_208_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_208_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_208_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_208_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_208_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 209, 25 June 1977, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Shadows... / B. C. E. Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Nora Post, oboe; Martha Hannemann, soprano; Paul Schmidt, speaker; Thomas Halpin, violin; Baird Contemporary Ensemble Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Program entitled: Shadows, puppets, and clowns (program 2; Side B entitled: Baird Contemporary Ensemble from a concert dated 13 May 1977 Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 209)
    Contents: Neuwirth: Von Unklaich nach China; Mikhashoff: Last words of Chief Seattle; Gilman: The curlew -- The dream of death; Loomis: L'heure exquise; Ogden: Pour un tombeau de Jean Cocteau; Cowell: Ostinato pianissimo; Mikhashoff: In memoriam: Benjamin Britten